方才我们说过了  Android框架不允许我们
When we said that the framework didn't want us
在主线程上执行网络操作工作
to run network operations on the main thread, what
那什么是主线程呢  Android程序默认是
is the main thread? Well, Android apps run by
在主线程上执行的  也叫UI进程
default on the main thread, also called the UI thread.
它控制着所有用户的输入和输出
It handles all the user input as well as
比如绘制屏幕等
the output, such as screen drawing. Thus we want
因此我们就得避免在这里有任何耗时的操作
to avoid any time-consuming operations here, otherwise the UI
不然界面就要卡顿  让这些需要花费大量时间的工作
is going to stutter. Instead, kick off a background worker
交给后台去做
thread if you have to do some long-running
这包括网络请求  图片解码  或者
work. This includes doing network calls, decoding bitmaps, or
读取  写入数据库
reading, and writing from the database. Okay. So, somehow,
所以  我们需要把网络请求部分的代码从主线程移走
we have to move the networking code off the
但是要怎么做才行呢
main thread. But how are we going to do
这里有一些选项
that? Well there are several options, but let's look
但是让我们先来回答一个问题  找到这个类的名称
for the name of the Android class that simplifies
这个类简化了后台线程的创建和UI线程的同步处理
background thread creation and UI thread synchronization, so that
它将在后台执行操作并把结果返回给主线程
the results from the background work will come back onto the
然后我们可以用这个结果来更新我们的用户界面
main thread, and then we can use it to update our
去网上搜索一些这个类的名称  填入下面的
UI. Search online and figure out the answer to this question
方框里吧  我有一些建议
and then enter the class name in the box. Here's some
如果你有一些问题无法从
advice for you. If you ever get stuck on how to
Android开发者网站上找到结果的话
do something in Android and you can't find it on the
你可以尝试一下stackoverflow.com这个网站
developer's site you can try to check stackoverflow.com. It's a question
这是一个对Android开发者来说非常重要的一个问答网站
and answer site that many Android developers use as a valuable resource.
你可能会碰到一些人问了跟你
So chances are likely that someone has
相同或者相近的问题
already asked a similar question that you have.